欧洲队 13-5 世界队 · 赛后捧杯致辞
let's hear it
掌声送给
for the Laver Cup champions, Team Europe,
拉沃尔杯冠军 欧洲队
and they're led by Captain Yannick Noah,
队长雅尼克 诺阿
Vice-Captain Tim Henman, Arthur Fery,
副队长亨曼 阿瑟 费里
Casper Ruud, Jakub Mensik,
卡斯珀 鲁德 门西克
Rafael Jodar, Flavio Cobolli,
霍达尔 科博利
Carlos Alcaraz and Alexander Zverev.
阿尔卡拉斯和兹维列夫
But before we get
不过在我们
to lift the trophy we're all looking forward
举起奖杯之前 我们都很想
to hearing from Yannick Noah
听听雅尼克 诺阿怎么说
the microphone is yours first
话筒交给你 首先
of all I would like to thank Roger
我要感谢罗杰
for having this great idea years ago
多年前想出这个好主意
to make this Laver Cup.
办起了拉沃尔杯
so Roger congratulations I'm really grateful
罗杰 恭喜你 我真的很感激
to participate in my humble way
能以我微薄的方式
on this journey I would like
参与这段旅程 我还想
to thank also Tony, all the team, Tony,
感谢托尼和整个团队 托尼
and Andre I have a special message
还有安德烈 我有句话要对你说
to you I really appreciate the fact
我真的很感激
that you let me win once I'm really full
你让我赢了一次 我满怀
of gratitude you know I know you're
感激 你知道 我知道你是
a good guy at the beginning I thought you
好人 一开始我以为你
were a good guy but now I know thank you
是好人 现在我确定了 谢谢你
for letting us win I would like to thank
让我们赢 我想感谢
my team you guys you know I don't know
我的队员们 你们知道 我不知道
if I'm a captain
我算不算队长
but most of all I think maybe you see me
但更重要的是 你们也许把我
as your father
当成父亲
or maybe your grandfather maybe
或者祖父 也许
your uncle I'll never forget
是叔叔 我永远不会忘记
this very special moment
这个非常特别的时刻
that I share with you you know we all try
和你们一起分享 我们都努力
to play we all have to play
去打 我们都得上场
but sometimes winning feels good
但赢球的感觉真好
so I'm really happy that for once you won
我真的很高兴 这一次你们
for me so congratulations guys
为我赢了 恭喜你们 伙计们
and thank you all for supporting
也谢谢大家的支持
this unbelievable weekend we had
这个不可思议的周末
some great matches as you all know it
精彩的比赛不少 你们都知道
could have gone any any way and you know
结果本来怎样都有可能
so we won some tiebreakers, we've
我们赢了几个抢七
been lucky at times so I hope
有时候也有运气 希望
to see you soon thank you very much bye
很快再见 非常感谢 再见
bye well thank you Yannick well there's
再见 谢谢雅尼克
only one thing left to do and Yannick if you
现在只剩最后一件事 雅尼克
could come back down the line it is time
请你再走回来 是时候
for you and your team to lift the Laver Cup
让你和队友们举起拉沃尔杯
over to you. Come on, boys. It's one piece.
交给你们了 来吧伙计们